dragonballz.com 2015-06-07

# Dragon Ball Z | privacy

Sign Up for Updates

FUNimation Entertainment is respectful about the privacy of our users. As a general policy, no personal information is automatically collected from users of our sites. This policy statement tells you how we collect information from you and how we use it. Certain non-personal information of users is recorded by the standard operation of the FUNimation Internet servers. Such information is used to make your visits to our sites easy and enjoyable. Other uses of this information include internal review of the number of visitors to FUNimation’s sites, but only in an aggregate form. E-mail addresses and other personally identifiable information about users of this site are known to FUNimation only when voluntarily submitted. However, be assured that FUNimation will not disclose your personal information to third parties without your consent. FUNimation may, however, disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) FUNimation’s intellectual property rights or the rights of other FUNimation site users, or to anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Further, FUNimation may disclose user information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. 

Personal information that may be collected in connection with users voluntarily filling out contest entry forms, purchasing FUNimation’s products, joining FUNimation, or replying to a survey is retained by FUNimation and is not sold or otherwise transferred to a third party, except that FUNimation may provide this information in an aggregate form to third parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. FUNimation needs to collect this information for fulfilling prizes, tracking/verifying compliance with FUNimation policies as well as federal, state, and local laws, and for editorial and feedback solicitation purposes. We also use this information to better understand our fans’ use of our sites so that we can enhance our users’ enjoyment of our sites. 

###  Use of Cookies 

Some information may also be automatically collected (unless you have set your computer’s preferences to prevent it) whenever you log onto FUNimation websites through what are known as “cookies.” Cookies are pieces of information stored on a user’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. A cookie cannot determine your name, e-mail address, phone number, or any other personal information about you unless you choose to provide that information. Rather, a cookie is able to store information about your computer and the online activities generated from it, such as what kind of browser software you use to access the Internet, the type of operating system, and the domain name of your Internet service provider. 

We may also use cookies to give users the ability to personalize the website or track and provide users’ scores on designated games or contests. This information is most easily tracked with cookies and is used only for the purpose of operating the website and administrative and research functions. 

###  Privacy Policy Manager 

Attn: Privacy Policy Manager 

1200 Lakeside Pkwy 

Flower Mound, TX, 75028 USA 

+1-972-355-7300 

### Sign up today and get exclusive news and offers from Funimation!
